(FAINT DIN)
(DIN GROWS LOUDER)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CHILDREN EXCLAIM)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(P.A. SYSTEM CHIMES)
ANNOUNCER:
Attention. customers.
The pool is now closed.
Please make
your way to the exit.
(PEOPLE CHATTER)
(PEOPLE CHATTER AND LAUGH)
(CREAKING)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(WATER DRIPS QUIETLY)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(SIGHS)
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
(SHOWER RUNS)
(FOOTSTEPS RETURN)
What are you doing here?
(SHOWER CONTINUES TO RUN)
(LIFEGUARD BREATHES HEAVILY)
(LIFEGUARD MOANS)
(CONTINUES MOANING)
(MOANS)
(STOPS MOANING)
(MOANS FAINTLY) OK.
-(SHOWER STOPS ABRUPTLY)
-(LIFEGUARD GASPS)
-(LOUD THUMP)
-(LIFEGUARD SCREECHES)
(LOUD THUMP AND CLATTER)
(LIFEGUARD WHIMPERS)
(WAILS)
(GROANS)
(SCREECHES)
(SCREECHING FADES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(WIND BLOWS)
-(RYAN CHUCKLES)
-Wait. Fuck. Don't.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Stop.
(FAINT CROAKING)
Fuckin' hell.
Calm the fuck down.
(INSECTS BUZZ)
(FAINT HISSING)
(FROG CROAKS WEAKLY)
(LOUD SCRAPING)
(RYAN GRUNTS)
(BIRDS CHIRP IN DISTANCE)
Oh.
Reckon I could get up there?
What?
Snakes and heights.
Right. (CHUCKLES)
(LANDS LOUDLY)
(WINGS FLAP)
(RYAN SIGHS)
(RUBBLE SCATTERS)
(TIMBER BOARD TAPS LIGHTLY)
(RYAN CHUCKLES) Fuck me.
(RYAN DROPS TIMBER BOARD)
(LOUD CLANG)
(ROCK CLATTERS)
-(BOULDER SCRAPES)
-(DUST DISPERSES)
(GRUNTS)
(LOUD CLANGING)
-(GROANS)
-(LOUD METALLIC CLANG)
What makes you think
you can pick that up?
I can do it.
(METAL DRAGS)
(GROANS)
(METAL CLANKS LOUDLY)
(SNIGGERS)
RYAN: Oh. fuck.
Funnel-web.
On your shoulder.
Just don't move. alright?
(RYAN FLICKS)
(RYAN LAUGHS)
Fuck you. you cunt.
(RYAN CHUCKLES) What?
What the fuck was that?
Do it one more time.
(BOTH GROAN)
Fuck.
Fuck you doing?!
There anything
you're not afraid of?
Huh?
(RYAN BREATHES HEAVILY)
(NAIM GRUNTS)
(PANTS HEAVILY)
(NAIM MOANS)
(GASPS)
We should go.
(TRAIN HORN BLOWS IN DISTANCE)
Yeah. OK.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know. is it a good
thing or a bad thing? Is it...
It's not even a thing.
Yeah. but. like. come on.
Come on. what?
You ignore me at school
and then you just ask me
to hang out?
Like. it doesn't make
any sense.
I don't ignore you.
NAIM: Yes. you do.
We're at school.
you're so different.
And then you're with just me.
RYAN: Give me a fucking
example of how I'm different.
-NAIM: Hmm.
-Hmm. Hmm.
-By the way you act. talk...
-Can't think of one.
..speak. walk.
Everything about you.
I'm the exact same cunt
I've always been. mate.
You're not.
(GRUNTS)
RYAN: Get down. Get down.
Get off me.
NAIM: OK.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(SPARSE MUSIC)
Been there before?
The...the mill?
Nah. First time.
(BICYCLES CLICK)
RYAN: You?
Yeah. first time.
NAIM: Cool.
(BIRDS CAW)
Don't tell anyone about it.
The mill.
Yeah. nah. I...I won't.
(BICYCLE CLICKING SLOWS.
THEN STOPS)
See you later?
Yeah.
(SPARSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
PASTOR: Will she accept love
into her life?
And by accepting God's love.
she will be prepared
to make free choices.
The free choices
that will bring her here.
-To confess her sins.
-(BABY FUSSES QUIETLY)
Because we recognise
both the physical
and the spiritual
responsibility of parenthood.
(BABY FUSSES)
PASTOR: Now I'm sure
you're all sick of
the sound of my voice.
-(CONGREGATION LAUGHS)
-I know I am.
So I'd love it if we could
all come together now
and pray for this little one.
-(UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYS)
-♪ Blackest shadows
♪ In the poison
Taste it
♪ Call my name
♪ And I would come to face it
♪ Everything that you created
♪ Yeah
♪ Everything that is broken
washes away
♪ I turn to you. my devotion
Show me the way
♪ Everything that is sacred
softens the pain
♪ I know it's you
I'm not shaken
♪ Show me the way
♪ Everything that is broken
washes away
♪ I turn to you. my devotion
Show me the way
♪ Everything that is sacred
softens... ♪
How old do you reckon
that mum was?
Naim!
Probably 12.
But. you know. there are
older kids here too.
Mum.
Sally Frankston's into
that psych trance stuff
you listen to.
It's actually. um. psytrance
and I haven't listened to it
since we moved here.
You haven't made
any friends either.
Mum. don't.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
Psytrance?
How long have I
been calling it psych?
About three years.
I bet you thought
that was funny.
Still do.
PASTOR: Arlene.
You. uh. you must be Naim.
I'm Rod.
Uh. you...you know my son.
Hunter. from school.
HUNTER: Hey. bro.
Arlene. have you. um. have you
thought about it some more?
Your story?
I mean. it really. really
doesn't have to be much.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(NAIM EXHALES)
(INHALES SLOWLY)
(EXHALES)
And it was. um. it was late
and the sky had this.
like. orange stripe in it.
(SIGHS) And. um...
There was these bells.
like. these fake tinny bells.
and she was just like.
"God's ringing for you. Naim.
"Listen."
And I just said.
"Mum. I'm sick of
your fucking bullshit.
"It's just a fucking
ice-cream truck."
(CHUCKLES)
And then she just said.
"One day. one day. Naim.
"you'll...you'll believe in
things that you can't see."
And then she laughed
some more.
She used to laugh a lot.
I shouldn't have told you
that. I'm...I'm sorry.
RYAN: You shouldn't be.
Do you like it here?
NAIM: What?
What do you like
about this place?
Nah. my...my mum
wanted to move here.
(SIGHS) Said she...belonged.
To what?
People who believed.
I don't know.
Some...some bullshit.
Now...stuck in this shithole.
So...nothing then?
What?
There's nothing you like
about this place?
(CHUCKLES)
Nah.
(SOFTLY) Nothing.
(SPARSE ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
ARLENE: I knew what he was
doing. He was just walking.
Because if he was
out there walking.
we wouldn't
have to talk about it.
I knew this awful thing
was coming for Tom.
For both of us. really.
And I'd just sit at home
in this terrifying silence.
But I found someone else
in that silence.
Someone who'd listen.
Who'd talk about death.
but...above all. about life.
Jesus is in that silence.
And I love that silence now.
It makes me feel...safe.
(STUDENTS CHUCKLE AND SNIGGER)
STUDENT: "Die not. poor Death
"Nor yet canst thou kill me
"From rest and sleep
"Which but thy pictures be
"Much pleasure; then from thee
much more must flow.
"And soonest our best..."
(WIND BLOWS)
(BIRD CAWS)
-(METAL CREAKS)
-(HEAVY BREATHING)
-(ROCK STRIKES)
-(HILLS HOIST CREAKS)
-(GRUNTS)
-(ROCK STRIKES)
-(HILLS HOIST CREAKS)
-(WASHING FLAPS)
-(ROCK STRIKES)
-(HUNTER GROANS)
(HUNTER GRUNTS)
(ROCK STRIKES)
(RYAN GRUNTS)
(SOMBRE MUSIC)
(HILLS HOIST
CONTINUES TO CREAK)
(WASHING FLAPS)
(NAIM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(WIND WHISTLES)
(DARK MUSIC)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SNIFFS)
Really?
(DARK MUSIC CONTINUES)
No.
(VOICE FADES)
(DOG BARKS)
(RAIN PATTERS)
ROD: Naim. you sure
we can't get you anything?
Tea. water. juice?
How about a beer?
-He thinks he's funny.
-ROD: I am funny.
We don't drink.
JACKY: Izzie?
(CHAIR SCRAPES ON FLOOR)
Thank you.
So...
You. um...
You wanna tell us
what's going on?
Is your mum OK?
I know you've both been
through a lot.
You won't tell Hunter
I came by?
Please. don't tell
either of them.
-(BOUNCING BALL ECHOES)
-(STUDENTS CALL OUT)
(DARK MUSIC)
(ALL SPEAK INAUDIBLY)
(DARK MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC FADES)
RYAN: You. uh.
been to one of these before?
HUNTER: Yeah.
It's just another one
of these shows
my parents put on
for these gullible arseholes.
(RYAN CHUCKLES) Yeah. right.
My dad's one of them
fucking gullible arseholes.
Reckon that guy
can make it stop?
Make what stop?
-HEALER: You feel it?
-(SOFTLY) No. thanks.
HEALER: Tell us
what you're feeling.
(GLASSES CLINK)
Um...
It's kind of cold in here.
I guess.
(RYAN CHUCKLES)
That's good.
Cold is good.
There's glory
in all temperatures.
(HEALER MUTTERS INCANTATION)
All the suffering...
(CONTINUES MUTTERING)
(MUTTERS IN
BARELY AUDIBLE TONES)
(KISSES CROSS)
-(EXHALES)
-(WIND WHISTLES)
(SIGHS)
There you go.
That's your healing.
Do you feel it?
Uh. not...not really. no.
I just feel colder
than before.
HEALER: That's the power
of God closing in on you.
(BREATHES IN SHARPLY)
All your lust.
all your indecency.
all your desire.
it has to go now.
Not tomorrow but now.
-Right now.
-(LIGHTER CLICKS)
Now look.
Look at the light.
By the power
of your holy flame.
make new what was defiled.
Two fires. O Lord.
One to defile
and one to reform.
(HUNTER GAGS)
(HUNTER AND RYAN
WHEEZE AND GAG)
HEALER: The sons of Aaron
brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
-(HUNTER THUDS)
-JACKY: Rod. what's going on?
HEALER: So the fire
of judgement fell.
(RYAN GROANS AND THUDS)
-BILL: Ryan!
-ROD: Hunter?
JACKY: What's happening?
Hunter?
ROD: Hunter? Hunter?
What's happening?
JACKY: Rod. what's happening?
What's going on?
ROD: Please. Someone.
help him breathe! Please!
(SCREECHES)
HEALER: The sons of Aaron
brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
And so the fire
of judgement fell.
-ROD: Hunter!
-BILL: Hold his head.
ROD: Hunter! It's me.
Look at me.
(GAGS)
CATHY: Ryan. please!
(RYAN GROANS PAINFULLY)
HEALER:
By the fire that consumes.
I call upon the judgement.
Let the fire fall now!
(SCREAMS)
(GUTTURAL SCREAMING)
ROD: End it now!
CATHY: Somebody!
Somebody do something!
I'm scared here.
(HEALER'S VOICE ECHOES)
(CAR RATTLES)
-(SWITCHES ON CAR RADIO)
-♪ Doors are open
♪ And I believe
♪ I believe that
every mountain
♪ Has your name
carved in the bottom
♪ I believe
that every river... ♪
(SQUELCHING)
-(SPLAT!)
-STUDENT: Oh. Oh. my God.
(STUDENTS WHISPER)
(STUDENTS GASP)
-(STUDENTS LAUGH)
-Yeah.
What. cunt?
Fucking loser.
(TRAFFIC DRONES)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
TEENAGER: Oh! Oh!
Stay on the road. mate.
(CAR DOOR SHUTS)
(TROLLEY RATTLES)
TEENAGER:
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
(DOOR SQUEAKS SHUT)
(TEENAGERS OUTSIDE
LAUGH AND CHAT)
(LIQUID POURS)
Ryan?
Your mum's gonna see us.
They'll find out
about you too.
You OK?
(TEENAGER OUTSIDE LAUGHS)
Come on.
(LIQUID CONTINUES POURING)
You have to stop.
Stop what?
-I can't.
-ARLENE: Naim?
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
-(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
-(BREATHES SHAKILY)
TEENAGER: Oh. mate.
Let's go on the road. mate.
-(BUS DRONES PAST)
-(TROLLEY CLATTERS)
(TEENAGERS LAUGH)
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
(BIRD CAWS LOUDLY)
(HILLS HOIST SQUEAKS)
Told you not here.
They'll see us.
You sure there's no-one here?
(HILLS HOIST SQUEAKS)
Are you sure?
Come on then.
(BIRD SQUAWKS)
Come on.
(SCREEN DOOR SQUEAKS.
BACK DOOR OPENS)
RYAN: Be quiet. yeah?
(BACK DOOR CLOSES)
(FRONT DOOR SQUEAKS OPEN)
(FRONT DOOR SHUTS)
Lucky they're fucking always
hid away in their bedroom.
(GATE SQUEAKS)
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDE)
Yeah. but what
if there's people here?
-(DOOR OPENS)
-(POP MUSIC PLAYS)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(RYAN SPEAKS SOFTLY)
Yeah. OK. Let's just try it.
Thought you were scared.
-(PHOTO BOOTH WHIRRS)
-(PHOTOS EJECT)
-(BOOTH CLICKS)
Are you gonna do it too?
Just me.
-(BOOTH CLICKS)
-(PHOTOS EJECT)
(GIRL LAUGHS)
GIRL: Oh. my God.
That's pathetic.
-(RYAN SHRIEKS)
-(BOOTH CLICKS. PHOTOS EJECT)
-(RYAN WHEEZES)
-(DARK MUSIC)
(NAIM SCREAMS)
(RYAN PANTS)
(GROANS)
-NAIM: Ryan. Ryan!
-(RYAN GRUNTS)
-(RYAN PANTS)
-(LOUD BANG)
-(RATTLING)
-Fuck.
-Stop following me!
-Ryan. Ryan.
Stop doing this.
Stop coming to my house.
What was that?
(YELLS) You!
It was you!
Please. don't make me
tell anyone.
Just leave me alone.
Please.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDE)
(POP MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(NAIM BREATHES HEAVILY)
WOMAN: Hey!
Chips!
NAIM: That guy at your house
the other night.
what did he do to you?
HUNTER: It's worked
on kids all over.
In Redbay. there was a girl.
There was a guy in Mount
Harvey had it done to him.
He's got kids now.
That's what I heard.
So did it work?
On you?
Why are you asking?
What about Ryan?
Did it work on him?
It's every night.
When I close up...
..he comes here.
He shouldn't be
doing it anymore.
Doing what?
He just throws shit at me.
-No. right.
-When he comes here.
-No. I just meant...
-We don't do anything else.
Why doesn't anyone
fucking believe me?
WOMAN: Hunter!
(DARK MUSIC)
(RAIN PATTERS SOFTLY)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR ALARM BEEPS)
(NAIM BREATHES HEAVILY)
(DOOR CLICKS OPEN)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(OUTSIDE DOOR CLOSES)
(GARBAGE RATTLES)
(HUNTER BREATHES HEAVILY)
(GARBAGE CLATTERS)
-(ROCK THUDS)
-(HUNTER GRUNTS)
-(CLATTERING)
-(ROCK THUDS)
-(HUNTER GROANS)
-Hunter! Hunter!
-(HUNTER BREATHES HEAVILY)
Hunter. no!
(DOOR RATTLES)
-Hunter. stop!
-(HUNTER GAGS)
-(GROANS)
-(DOOR RATTLES)
(HUNTER GAGS)
No. stop!
(HUNTER SHRIEKS)
-(DOOR BANGS)
-Hunter!
Hunter. no. Stop!
Hunter! Hunter!
-(DOORKNOB RATTLES)
-Hunter! Hunter!
-(HUNTER SCREECHES)
-NAIM: Oh. Hunter. no!
-(HUNTER WAILS)
-Hunter. Wait!
-(NAIM GRUNTS)
-(DOOR BANGS)
-(HUNTER CONTINUES SCREECHING)
-(NAIM GRUNTS)
-NAIM: Hunter?! Hunter?!
-(SCREECHES IN DISTANCE)
(HUNTER'S SCREECHES ECHO)
NAIM: Hunter. where are you?
-Hunter!
-(DARK MUSIC)
(CICADAS CHIRP)
(DARK MUSIC)
(SPEAKS INAUDIBLY)
NAIM: It did something to him.
-Then that thing killed him!
-Alright. OK.
Naim. I am not your enemy. OK?
I'm here to help you but I can
only do that if you stay calm.
-(NAIM BREATHES SHAKILY)
-Alright?
Is everything OK at home?
You know. with you
and with your mum?
What?
Well. it's just sometimes
when we're dealing with
something
and it's too hard to accept.
we deny it.
You know. we push it away.
We try to replace that truth
with something else.
-Another story.
-I felt it at the servo.
And I felt it
at the photo booth!
WOMAN: Naim. OK?
We all want the same thing.
The police are working on it.
But...
..if you really wanna help us.
you have to be honest.
What you're describing.
this thing you're describing.
it sounds impossible.
It's coming for Ryan.
It's gonna kill him!
OK. they will come in here
and they will charge you
with disrupting
an investigation.
Can you just... Please!
Is that what
you want me to do?
Do anything. please! I just...
It's gonna kill him!
(CHAIR SCRAPES ON FLOOR)
WOMAN: Just...
-(WOMAN SIGHS)
-I've had this feeling...
..all my life that I'm...
..that I've been scared of.
And ever since we moved.
I really got
more scared of it.
Because Ryan and I...
..we shared the same feeling.
We got together.
Like. we got together.
And it was exciting.
But it totally made me
feel more scared.
(SOBS)
Now. I don't want you
to worry. OK?
-We'll speak to someone.
-Uh. Hunter's dad.
Um. I don't know.
He runs the church.
He might know
where to find that guy.
-The deliverance healer.
-We'll look into it.
I promise. OK?
(SOFTLY) Thank you.
OFFICER: Sergeant.
I'll be out in a minute.
(WOMEN SPEAK SOFTLY)
(WOMAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY)
(CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY)
-(CONVERSATION FADES)
-(DARK MUSIC)
(SEMITRAILER ENGINE REVS)
(ARLENE ENGAGES HANDBRAKE
AND REMOVES CAR KEYS)
NAIM: Who's that?
Mum?
ARLENE: I've been
thinking. Naim.
Maybe there's always
gonna be kids
who...hurt people like Hunter.
People like Ryan.
Like you.
That woman with the police
says she sees it all the time.
She reckons it's that kind of
hate that killed Hunter.
I just...
I can't lose you too.
I'm sorry.
Mum. no.
No. you can't do this.
-(NAIM WHIMPERS)
-ARLENE: Please. I can't.
No. you can't do this. Mum!
(NAIM GROANS) Mum! Mum!
Get off me!
MAN: Settle down.
NAIM: No. you can't do this!
Get off me!
Mum. they killed Hunter! Mum!
MAN: Mate. mate.
NAIM: You don't wanna do this!
-MAN: It's OK.
-Please. don't! Let go of me!
(DARK MUSIC)
Please!
No! Get off me!
HEALER: Naim. don't.
Hold still.
-NAIM: Argh! Stop touching me!
-(LIGHTER CLICKS)
-HEALER: Look.
-(NAIM SCREAMS)
HEALER: Look.
-(NAIM GROANS)
-HEALER: Look.
Two fires. O Lord.
One to defile
and one to reform.
(LIGHTER LID ECHOES)
(NAIM GAGS)
Sons of Aaron brought fire
to please themselves.
They worshipped
as they willed.
(HEALER VOICE ECHOES) So
the fire of judgement fell...
(HEALER CONTINUES
MUTTERING INCANTATION)
(NAIM GAGS)
(HEALER CONTINUES
MUTTERING INCANTATION)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(HEALER'S VOICE FADES)
(PEOPLE CHATTER QUIETLY)
ARLENE: Hey.
They have those sausage rolls.
The ones you like.
They have pizza too.
But it has olives on it.
I took the olives off.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDE)
(PEOPLE CHATTER INDISTINCTLY)
(BIRDS CAW)
Ryan?
Ryan. I've been trying
to find you.
Told you to fuck off.
NAIM: Ryan. just wait.
My mum took me to that guy.
-The deliverance healer.
-Why would she do that?
I don't know.
Ever since we moved here.
she can't face
anything that's real.
I don't know what to do.
(GENTLE MUSIC)
-(NAIM GROANS)
-(RYAN GRUNTS)
(DARK MUSIC)
Fuck!
(DARK MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
-NAIM: Help! Help!
-You right. mate?
-He tried to...
-Who?
Him!
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
(PEOPLE CHATTER INDISTINCTLY)
Ohh.
(NAIM BREATHES SHAKILY)
Fuck!
-(NAIM PANTS)
-RYAN: Hey! Naim.
Stay the fuck away from me!
You saw it. didn't you?
-What did it look like?
-IZZIE: Naim! Ryan.
They did it to you too.
didn't they?
Come with me.
Come on.
IZZIE: These kids
at a camp I went to.
they said a couple of girls
went to that guy.
the deliverance healer.
And after.
one of them died at the pool.
Some people said she slipped.
I don't know. I thought
it was just a dumb story.
So why are you telling us?
My brother...
My brother saw it.
I didn't believe it.
What about the other one?
You said the guy did it
to two of them.
Jessica.
And now she just hangs out
at the Murryville Hospital
all day and night.
Why?
It comes for you
when you're alone.
The hospital's
the only place that's...
ROD: Izzie.
your mum wants you.
Murryville. that's about
an hour away.
Right?
Do you think she's right?
About being alone with it?
(DARK MUSIC)
-(AIR BRAKES HISS)
-(TRAVELLERS CHATTER)
(PHONE LOCK CLICKS)
MAN: I'm sorry.
(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
NAIM: Jessica?
-(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
-You lost?
You knew a girl. Marnie?
(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
You kids shouldn't be in here.
We just wanna know
about that guy.
(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
-The deliverance healer.
-(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
Yeah. well. I don't know
where he is.
If you find him. trust me. you
don't want what he's selling.
(ELASTIC BAND SNAPS)
It's too late.
RYAN: What the fuck
is this thing?
NAIM: Well. what did you see?
It always looks like
the person you're the most...
You know.
Into.
And it doesn't matter
who it is.
Best friend. Movie star.
Gym teacher you once
had a crush on.
It knows.
So. um...
So you think Marnie saw you?
When she died?
Yeah. you can go now.
I can't help you.
No. I didn't mean...
Just stay around other people.
No. I shouldn't
have said that.
I said fuck off!
Sorry. We just thought you'd
know how to make it stop.
(SIREN WAILS IN DISTANCE)
You can't make it stop.
Nothing can make it stop.
(SIREN NEARS)
-We should have split up.
-MAN: Hey!
JESSICA: It gets better
at looking like you
and touching like you.
We've talked about this. Your
friends need to leave now.
I...I...I am serious.
MAN: Can we get some
security backup down here?
Stay away from your friend.
You are only making it worse.
You are only making it worse!
Stay away!
SECURITY: Come on. You're
not even a patient in here.
RYAN: Let's go. Naim. Come on.
(JESSICA SCREECHES)
(BUS HISSES)
(PEOPLE SPEAK INDISTINCTLY)
(CLANKING NOISE)
(EERIE MUSIC)
(DOOR HISSES)
Hey. you missed someone.
Can we let him on quickly?
Hey. you alright?
Naim.
(NAIM BREATHES HEAVILY)
Fuck.
Hey. hey. hey.
Hey. look at me. Naim.
Hey. it can't get you.
There's people right here.
Naim. It can't get you.
Hey. I'm here. Fuck. open it!
-Hey.
-(DOOR HISSES)
Hey. It's alright. Naim.
it's alright. It's alright.
Look at me. Hey. it's alright.
(BUS DRONES)
I'll go away.
What?
What if she's right?
What if we're only
making it stronger?
Don't go.
I hate that shithole anyway.
I know you do. Naim.
-You don't?
-Yeah. I do.
Don't go.
RYAN: It's all my fault.
(SOFTLY) Please.
(KISSES)
(BELT UNBUCKLES)
(ZIPPER UNZIPS)
It's OK.
(MOANS SOFTLY)
(NAIM'S BREATHING QUICKENS)
(KISSES)
(NAIM MOANS)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
BOY: Oh. my God.
You're hopeless.
(STUDENTS CHATTER
INDISTINCTLY)
(GIRL LAUGHS) Yeah.
she should get away with you.
(GIRL LAUGHS)
(STUDENTS CHATTER
INDISTINCTLY)
GIRL: Thanks. yeah.
'Cause. like. I know. like.
they'll be. like.
getting the bus.
-I don't want her with us.
-Yeah.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(STUDENT LAUGHS)
I'm gonna miss it again!
-(GRUNTS)
-GIRL: I'm so sorry.
(RUNNING FOOTSTEPS)
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
-(RYAN SCREAMS)
-(DOOR OPENS)
RYAN: Ohh! (FALLS TO GROUND)
-GIRL: Ryan?
-BOY: Ryan!
-GIRL: Oh. Oh. my God!
-BOY: In here!
GIRL: OK. Ryan. um.
just...just. like...
Wait. Ryan. just wait.
(RYAN SOBS)
-(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
-GIRL: What happened?
-(GROANS)
-GIRL: Who...who did that?
(PANTS)
-Oh. my God.
-Oh! Oh!
(GIRL WAILS)
(DARK MUSIC)
(ROD SOBS)
(ROB SOBS)
I know you miss him.
(STAMMERS INDISTINCTLY)
-(ROD SOBS)
-(JACKY KISSES)
Come on. please. honey.
Come home.
-(SOBS)
-Come home. please.
Come home with me. Come home.
Please come home.
Please. honey.
NAIM: Bus we took
to Murryville.
Goes to the city.
Don't follow me.
What?
You shouldn't be near me.
I shouldn't be
near you either.
Right.
(SIGHS)
OK. so you leave town.
Then what?
It's just gonna look like
the next dickhead you're into.
And the next one after that.
If I'm gonna live with
this thing. then...
..I don't want it to look like
some other dickhead.
I want it to look like you.
(DARK ELECTRONIC MUSIC)
(DARK MUSIC CONTINUES)
You sure your parents
aren't gonna freak?
About the car.
IZZIE: Nuh. My dad's the one
who told me where to find him.
That guy that did this to you.
He'll know
how to take it back.
(EXHALES STRONGLY)
NAIM: Where is he?
What is this. Izzie?
NAIM: He's gonna do it here?
(VEHICLE APPROACHES)
Izzie?
IZZIE: My dad left yesterday.
He just packed up his stuff
and left.
Izzie. what the fuck
is going on?
He told me I didn't do
anything wrong.
He said I should stop
blaming myself
for what happened to Hunter.
(VEHICLE PULLS UP)
It only happened because of
how you made him feel.
(VEHICLE ENGINE STOPS)
And because you told
my parents about it.
(VEHICLE DOORS OPEN)
Do you wanna tell him
or should I?
Ryan...
Naim. what the fuck's
she talking about?
What are we doing out here?
(CHUCKLES)
Shouldn't be out this late.
you know?
Two boys...
..like you.
-(GRUNTS)
-Ryan!
-Come on!
-Let's get the sticks!
-Bitch!
-Ryan!
-(GRUNTS)
BOY: Hit him in the head!
Come on!
(PANTS)
-(BOTH GRUNT)
BOY: Hold him down.
-Grab him!
-(THUMP!)
(CHILLING MUSIC)
-IZZIE: Ryan. stop!
-(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
That's my parents' car!
-BOY: Watch out!
-Ryan!
IZZIE: Ryan. wait!
IZZIE: Ryan!
(ENGINE REVS)
Ryan.
-I'm sorry.
-Go inside.
I only told them about
you and Hunter because...
Get out of the car.
Now.
(UNCLIPS SEATBELT)
OK.
Naim.
If you see anything
that looks like me...
..don't go near it.
It won't be me.
-Ryan...
-It'll never be me.
(NAIM SIGHS)
(ENGINE REVS)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(SPARSE MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(SPARSE MUSIC CONTINUES)
What the fuck?!
(SCREAMS)
(PANTS)
(CHILLING MUSIC)
(DOG BARKS)
(NAIM GROANS)
(DARK MUSIC)
(PANTS)
(FLOOR CREAKS)
(SOFTLY) Mum?
Mum?
(DOOR CREAKS)
What's going on?
You can't leave me alone
like that.
What are you talking about?
There's this thing. It comes
when no-one else is around.
What thing?
It looks like Ryan.
There's a kid that
looks like Ryan?
-He do something to you?
-No. It's not like that.
It just looks like Ryan
'cause it always looks like...
Like what? Can you show me?
No-one else can see it.
Only us.
Mum.
Mum. did you hear what I said?
I think sometimes at your age
other kids can make you feel
a whole lot of things
you don't really feel.
I think Ryan
got in your head...
No. it's not that.
..and made you
believe in something
-that's not really you.
-(BANGS COUNTERTOP)
-What did he do to me?!
-Naim.
-OK. to us?
-Naim!
Surely you know
something about it!
Naim. stop.
Please don't lie to me.
And please... (GRABS KEYS)
..move your stuff
from my room.
You'll need to make
your own dinner.
(UNSETTLING MUSIC)
(SPARSE MUSIC)
(CHILLING MUSIC)
(NAIM RUNS AWAY AND PANTS)
(PANTS)
(DOOR BANGS SHUT)
(NAIM BREATHES STEADILY)
(METAL CLUNKS)
(CLUNKING CONTINUES)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(SWITCH CLICKS)
(DRIP CLUNKS)
-(SWITCH CLICKS)
-(NAIM GASPS)
(PHONE CLICKS)
(PHONE RINGING TONE)
ARLENE: This is Arlene.
Leave a message. thanks.
-(BEEP!)
-(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(PHONE CLICKS)
(DOOR RATTLES)
-(BANGING ON DOOR)
-(NAIM GASPS)
Naim.
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLES)
Naim. Open the door.
Open the fucking door.
That thing's in the backyard.
Shut up. Shut up. No. no.
I'm alone.
I know it's not you.
I don't know
if it's you either. do I?
I don't wanna be here.
I hate what
you fucking did to me.
My mum will be back soon.
She'll be pissed
if she sees you.
Yeah. but the point is
she'll see me. won't she?
Can't I just stay here then?
Until she gets back?
You know.
this is what they wanted.
Us to be scared of each other.
I am.
No. I've seen you scared.
Snake with a frog
in its mouth.
Thought you were gonna.
like. gag or something.
Fuck you.
'cause you were scared too.
Ryan.
I'm sorry I told them.
About you and Hunter.
(SIGHS)
I think I was scared.
How I felt.
About you.
I was never scared
of this. Naim.
(NAIM SIGHS) It's so dumb.
Yeah.
(NAIM GRUNTS)
Ahh!
(PANTS)
(PANTS RAPIDLY)
(CHILLING MUSIC)
(CLATTERING)
(SCREEN DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(GRUNTS)
(BODY THUDS)
-(RYAN GRUNTS)
-(NAIM GROANS)
(TWO LOUD THUMPS)
(BODY THUDS)
(NAIM GRUNTS)
Ahh! Ahhhh!
-(RYAN GRUNTS)
-(NAIM GROANS)
(LOUD BANGING)
(NAIM GRUNTS)
RYAN: No. no. no. no. no.
(NAIM GROANS)
(MOANS)
(NAIM GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
-(NAIM GRUNTS)
-(FLESH SQUELCHING)
(CHOKING)
(STABS)
(INTENSE MUSIC)
(GROANS)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(OTHER-WORLDLY SCREAM)
(GAGS)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(NAIM PANTS FRANTICALLY)
We're gonna close
in. like. 10 minutes.
(NAIM PANTS)
(MACHINE BEEPS)
Do you see that guy?
CASHIER: No.
And we're closing in...
..nine minutes.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
Hey. can I please just stay?
Just for a little bit?
CASHIER: Um...
No. you can close up.
I just...
I need to be around people.
Can I. please?
Please.
Just one. Yeah.
Just one person. please.
Anyone.
Just...just one person.
Please.
(DOG BARKS)
(TENSE MUSIC)
(PANTS FRANTICALLY)
(GRUNTS)
Ryan?
It's...it's me.
(GRUNTS)
(RYAN GRUNTS)
(DARK MUSIC)
(PANTS HEAVILY)
-(GRUNTS)
-(CRASH!)
(GRUNTS)
(GAGS)
-(METALLIC CLANG)
-(LIGHTER CLINKS)
(METALLIC CLANG)
-(NAIM GRUNTS)
-(FLAME BURSTS)
(OTHER-WORLDLY SCREAM)
(RYAN GROANS)
(MOANS)
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
(GRUNTS)
(RYAN WAILS)
(RYAN SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
RYAN: Naim!
It's me.
It's OK.
Please.
this is what it wanted.
It's OK.
They wanted us to be scared.
(LOUD CLANGING)
-(RYAN SCREAMS)
-Fuck.
(RYAN BANGS AGAINST WALL)
(RYAN SCREAMS)
(SCREAM ECHOES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
VOICEMAIL: This is Ryan.
-Leave a message.
-(BEEP!)
-(BIRDS SQUAWK)
-(PHONE CLICKS)
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(OMINOUS MUSIC)
(DOG BARKS)
WOMAN OVER RADIO: Don't
climb up on anything in there.
If you see the boy.
if you need assistance.
wait for the paramedics.
(WOMAN CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Hey.
It'll be OK.
I reckon he just ran away.
I've been here before.
With Ryan.
I know you don't believe me...
..but ever since
you took me to that guy...
..I've been getting hurt.
Ryan's been getting hurt too.
Mum. Mum.
I can't help you.
What?
This thing can't be undone.
That's what they told me.
You knew?
They told me
it would keep you safe.
But I'm not safe.
I'm terrified!
I know.
Look. I won't be
around forever.
And we need fear. Naim.
It's how we survive.
MAN OVER RADIO:
He's not in the middle.
Let's move to
the second field. Over.
(RADIO BLEEPS)
What did they tell you?
Mum!
WOMAN: Gather up this way.
We're moving on.
ARLENE: Come on.
It's getting cold.
MAN OVER RADIO:
Let the volunteers know
the boy's not here.
We're gonna move on. Over.
(COLD MUSIC)
MAN: Just a couple of
tinnies today. thanks.
Naim?
Naim!
(FRANTICALLY) Naim!
(VEHICLE APPROACHES)
(BRAKES SQUEAL)
(BUS DOOR CLUNKS OPEN)
(PEOPLE CHATTER INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Oh. my back does not
go well on those seats at all.
Oh. that's alright.
My back hurts.
Please tell me
it's really you.
(SIGHS)
(SONG PLAYS ON EARPHONES)
♪ 'Cause you see me like a UFO
♪ That's like never...
What?
Hey.
♪ 'Cause I made you use
your self-control
♪ And you made me lose
♪ My self-control.
my self-control... ♪
(CHILLING MUSIC)
♪ Keep a place for me
♪ I'll sleep between y'all.
it's nothing
♪ Keep a place for me
♪ It's nothing. it's nothing
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it
♪ Yeah
♪ I. I. I know you gotta
leave. leave. leave
♪ Take down some summertime
♪ Give up. just tonight.
night. night
♪ I. I. I know you got
someone comin'
♪ You're spittin' game.
know you got it... ♪
(WARM MUSIC)
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org